CURRICULUM VITAE OF MD. SHOHANUR RAHMAN

Cell: 01750-519157

Email: shohanur.rahman57@gmail.com

Experience: 4 Years.



Career Objective:

My objective is to fulfill self actualization need by shouldering adequate organizational responsibilities and ensure organizational as well as personal growth. I believe that, my confidence and activities will provide my with necessary knowledge to handle my kind of job.

Career Summary:

Software Engineer with through hands-on experience in all levels of testing, including performance, functional, integration, system regression, and user acceptance testing. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streaming process and efficiently resolving project issues.

Educational Qualification:

| Examination | Institute | Board | Result | Year |
|--------------|---------------------------|------------------------|---------------|--------------------------|
| BSc in CSE | University of Information | | Not Yet | 2 nd Semester |
| | Technology and Sciences | | | Running. |
| Diploma in | Rangpur Polytechnic | Bangladesh Technical | 2.96 out of 4 | 2015 |
| Computer | Institute | Education Board, Dhaka | CGPA | |
| Dakhil (SSC) | Bara Rangpur karamotia | Bangladesh Madrasah | 4.88 out of 5 | 2009 |
| | Kamil Madrasah | Education Board, Dhaka | GPA | |

Language Known:

Mother tongue Bengal & reasonable command both in spoken and written English.

Working Skills:

HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery, Kendo UI, Visual Basic, MSSQL, Asp.Net, C#, WCF, MVC, PHP, MySQL, WordPress, Responsive Web Design, Woocommerce.

| Asp.Net: | I have good experienced in Asp.Net (both Web Form & MVC) with good skilled on Razor, WCF, Entity Frame work, Web API. |
|-----------|--|
| Kendo UI: | I have good experienced about kendo framework. Kendo components like Grid, Editors, Charts, Scheduler etc. |
| SQL | I have good experienced in SQL server 2012, 2014. Large scalable database design with high functionality and stored procedure. |
| WordPress | I have good experienced in WordPress Custom Theme development, Psd to Wordpress, HTML to WordPress, Theme option setting, Option Tree, Plugin development and Integration. |
| UI | I have good experienced in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 3 & 4, jQuery, jQuery library functions, jQuery sorting, jQuery data table, Validation, Animation, Toggle, Ajax, JSON, All required event etc. |

Working History:

| Company | Designation | Duration |
|--------------------|-------------------------------|--------------------------------|
| UniSoft System | Software Engineer (Part time) | 03 Dec 2018 to Present |
| ParonSoft Solution | Software Engineer | 10 May 2015 to 30 Nov 2018 |
| Finch Data Soft | Web & Software Developer | 20 March 2014 to 30 April 2015 |

Personal Information:

Name : Md. Shohanur Rahman

Father's name : Md. Reju Miah

Mother's name : Most. Shahanaj Begum

Present Address : 126 North Mugda, Dhaka-1214.

Permanent Address : Kachu Alutary, Post: Bhagirat Machhari, P.S- Kaunia, Dist- Rangpur.

Date of Birth : 11 January 1994. Nationality : Bangladeshi.

Religion : Islam.

Marital Status : Unmarried

Contact No. : 01750-519157

Portfolios:

http://www.leasingtobuyhouses.com/ (WordPress)

- http://momentomcollective.com/ (WordPress)
- http://noteprousa.com/ (WordPress)
- http://16minutesolution.com/ (WordPress)
- http://divisionalnews24bd.com/ (WordPress)
- http://admissiontravel.com/ (Asp.Net)
- http://ajantashopping.com/ (Asp.Net)
- https://rams-app.com/Login/Index (Asp.Net)

Visual basic project does not share for security. I have more 12 projects with Asp.Net and VB. Some are bellow:

- https://bitbucket.org/unitysoftnet/mealtracker (VB.Net)
- https://bitbucket.org/unitysoftnet/medicaljustice (VB.Net)
- https://bitbucket.org/unitysoftnet/student-association (VB.Net)
- https://bitbucket.org/unitysoftnet/unitylive(Asp.Net)
- https://bitbucket.org/unitysoftnet/fisher (Asp.Net)

The information that I have given above is to the best of my knowledge, accurate and complete.

Reference (s):

| | Reference: 1 | Reference: 2 | |
|---------------|----------------------------------|-------------------------|--|
| Name: | Md.Fuad Mohammad Touhidul Ashraf | Md. Riad Ahmed | |
| Organization: | Rangpur Polytechnic Institute | | |
| Designation: | Instructor tech computer | Software Engineer | |
| Address: | Rangpur Sadar, Rangpur | | |
| Mobile: | 01716-752744 | 01931-523307 | |
| E-Mail: | fmt.ashraf102@yahoo.com | riadbaradanga@yahoo.com | |
| Relation: | Academic | Professional | |



25 Nov 2019